(Sheldon:)- Well?
- I reiterate. Knuckle under.
Oh, no, no, no. It is on.
I'm gonna introduce your friend
to a world of hurt.
(Leonard:)Oh, Penny,
you don't wanna get into it with Sheldon.
The guy's one lab accident away
from being a super villain.
(Penny:)I don't care. I was in junior rodeo. I can
hogtie and castrate him in 60 seconds.
(Howard:)No need to neuter the nerd.
I can get you back online.
(Leonard:)There, see?
(Leonard:)Problem solved.
Voilà.
SHELDON:
Hello, puny insects.
(Sheldon(voice from Howards laptop):)As a consequence of your efforts
to circumvent my will...
(Sheldon(voice from Howards laptop):)...everyone is awarded
one additional strike.
(Leonard:)Thanks a lot, Howard.
(Howard:)What are you complaining about?
I'm the one who has to take the class again.
(Sheldon:)Oh!